SONG: ♪ Volare... ♪
MAN: ..nation-building
project...
KEVIN RUDD: ..new infrastructure
of the 21st century.
WOMAN: If there is
a buzzword in this Budget,
it's 'nation-building'.
ANTHONY ALBANESE:
Major infrastructure projects
right around the country.
MAN 2: Real projects,
real money.
MAN 3: A transformational
vision for the infrastructure
of the 21st century.
TONY ABBOTT:
I want to be known as the
infrastructure prime minister.
-Nation-building...
-Nation-building for recovery.
-..nation-building program...
-..nation-building...
-Nation-building.
SONG: ♪ We can sing
in the glow of... ♪
MAN: And if you would
assure Mr Tseow
that we are mindful
of his concerns
regarding the timing
of the agreement
and flexible as to
its implementation.
(MAN ON TELEPHONE
SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(MAN 2 ON TELEPHONE SPEAKS
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
INTERPRETER: Very good.
And that we look forward
to meeting him in person.
INTERPRETER:
What date is this meeting?
Oh, the date? The date is the...
The date is the, um...
have it here!
It's the 8th of the 8th,
so a very auspicious date for...
..with the...
the 8 is, um...
Is that date OK?
(INTERPRETER
SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
(MR TSEOW SPEAKS
CHINESE LANGUAGE)
INTERPRETER: He says yes.
(MUTTERS) He said
more than that, didn't he?
OK. Well, we look...
Thank you for your time.
-Thank you.
-BOTH: Thank you.
Wow. That was hard work.
What have we got next?
-Canberra. -Nice to speak
to someone in English.
-Yes, it will.
-Will that be all?
Oh, yes! Thank you. Sorry.
I'm onto it. Hugh?
OK, we need to really fast-track
that memorandum of understanding
for the Chinese.
Jim. Sorry, he's just on
some conference calls.
-Did you want me to grab him?
-No, no, no.
It looks serious. I just wanted
to...run something past you.
-What do you reckon?
-Wow.
-Is that the development?
-Come up a treat, hasn't it?
-It sure has!
-Yeah.
Just one little hiccup.
Or bit of a blip.
-A hiccup or a blip?
-Hugh.
More of a mix-up.
Just inside the front cover,
first paragraph down.
"This integrated
urban environment
"will boast leisure precincts,
"parklands
and dynamic open spaces
"in addition to its very own
community gardens."
-Stop.
-I have.
That's the bit.
'Community gardens'.
-That was never in our draft.
-(LAUGHS) I know!
Then how did it get there?
I guess someone upstairs
was trying to pump things up,
got a little carried away.
Well, let's just delete it.
-This has not been released?
-Not to everyone.
Is that the blip?
I mean, there's 10 different
gallery levels...
Have you got
a spare charger?
-I can get you mine.
-Not for a laptop, for a phone.
-Actually, can I...
-No, hang on.
-Can I call you back?
-I think I've got it.
-When do you board?
-All good.
I'll call you in two minutes.
Sorry about this. Sorry.
-Is something wrong?
-Just received this.
OK, I know what
you're gonna say.
There's sensitivities involved -
we're Nation Building Australia
and we've got a huge
Chinese investment.
-Is that with the Chinese?
-Shanghai Syndicate.
Tseow Holdings.
-Hmm. Didn't see that.
-What are you worried about?
-Have you looked at it?
-I negotiated it.
-Closely.
-(SIGHS) What have we missed?
No, you're not seeing the wood
for the trees, Tony. The logo.
What about it?
You got a $4 billion
public-private investment deal
and you're gonna use
that logo?
-(SNORTS) Don't think so.
-Sorry, what's the wood?
Actually, what's the trees?
-Jim!
-It slipped through the net.
This is what
the drafting process is for.
You add stuff, we add stuff. You
look at ours, we look at yours.
We run it past the developer,
we all agree,
and then it gets released.
-You're saying we missed a step?
-You added a community garden!
It's a couple of swings
and a seesaw.
That's a community playground.
Then what's a community garden?
They're like
big vegetable patches.
What for?
So people can grow
their own produce.
Why would you do that?
It's supposed to foster
a sense of neighbourhood,
social cohesion.
That rings a bell, social...
What was it again?
Cohesion.
-That's the phrase
the interviewer used! -What?
When he was talking
to the Planning Minister
about it on the radio.
-The radio?
-Radio National.
But the response was amazing.
Inbox full,
people applauding us.
Wanted to get involved.
And Stephanie Alexander -
two missed calls.
I don't think there's a place
for a community garden.
There must be somewhere
we can squeeze in
a couple of tomato plants.
(SIGHS) Maybe I...
I tell you what -
I'll leave it with you.
I can't even bring myself
to look at it.
Rhonda, I just hung up
on a federal minister.
Good, because we need to
get on top of this.
We're nation-builders.
For God's sake!
It looks like we're still
building the Snowy.
-What's wrong with it?
-Everything!
The font, the colours.
Tell me one thing it does well.
-It says who we are.
-Disagree.
-It doesn't speak to me.
-It's a logo.
I deal with a lot of
departments,
and this is the sort of thing
everyone's getting right,
whereas I look at this,
and what do I hear?
Nothing.
-What do you want it to say?
-"Hey, you!"
"Get excited, get ready,
"because Australia's
being built!"
OK, well, I'll take that...
"So get out of the way,
because the future's now. Bang!"
-OK. You done?
-Bang.
OK, well, I'll make a note
to think about it.
-No, we need to jump on this.
-Yep. Sure. Definitely.
-Yes?
-That minister phoned back.
Oh, great.
What line is she on?
No, I told her you were busy.
And I didn't quite get her name.
-I know her name.
-Phew! (LAUGHS)
-Can you get her back online?
-She would have boarded by now.
HUGH: We could put it here.
-That's a roundabout.
-Sorry, I just saw green.
-In front of the apartments?
-No, that's the promenade.
What about behind?
I think that puts it
in the shade.
-So?
-What would you grow?
Mushrooms?
What about here?
Uh, that is a car park.
Put the car park underground
and the gardens on top.
-It's a little expensive. -Then
put the gardens underground.
-In order to grow what?
-Mushrooms.
-Can we forget about mushrooms?
-Truffles.
-What about here?
-What is it?
-It's green.
-It's not a roundabout.
-Thanks for joining us...
-Joining us now with details...
MAN: The gardens are
offering local residents...
WOMAN: It's a vibrant
community garden.
WOMAN 2: ..a community garden
project that's different...
WOMAN 3: ..gardening's
a bit old-fashioned...
-Privileged to be part of it.
-The backyard of the future.
MAN 2: We need the rain, true,
but you need to keep
the topsoil, don't you?
Yeah. No, that was
loud and clear.
Yes, no, that was
loud and clear as well.
Sorry, if I could just...
Hello? Hello?
How's it going?
-Uh, good. Yeah, just spoke
to Garry Bennett. -Oh, great.
-The property developer for the
Woolarong... -I know who he is.
And I told him about
the community garden.
Yep. What did he say?
Want it with or without
the swearwords?
Without.
Uh, point one.
"It's the dumbest beeping idea
I've ever heard."
Two. "Tell her she's beeping
crazy." I think that's you.
"Listen, you beeping redheaded
twerp" - I think that's me -
"why would people buying
luxury beeping penthouses
"want to grow
a beeping lettuce?"
And then he became really angry.
Right.
-Karnsten?
-Karsten!
-Karnsten.
-Karsten.
Oh, sorry.
We did meet before, didn't we?
Karlsten's here. Yep.
-Tony?
-Yep?
Karnsten's here
for Rhonda's logo meeting.
Oh, no. Can Scotty do it?
I'm not in.
-But you are.
-But he doesn't know that.
Um, he does.
I should check these things,
shouldn't I?
-Yeah. Let's make this
really quick. -Gotcha.
Actually, if I'm not back in 10,
come and get me.
What do I say?
Say there's an urgent
phone call, something like that.
OK, got it. Gotcha.
Oh, and that minister
from the other day rang back.
Why didn't you
come and tell me?
You were in a meeting
with Scotty. I got her name.
I know her name!
In future, come and tell me.
Right. But check
if you're in first.
-Karsten.
-Tony!
-Welcome back.
-Scotty.
-All done?
-How good are these?
Tony, I know how you like to
get these things really moving,
so I've got them all set up
and ready to go.
So this should not take
more than an hour or two.
Right, I'll stop you there.
I like that one.
-I don't. -I do.
-None of these are ours.
-Sorry? -They're copyrighted.
-Can't we change it a little?
I think
that's a bit dangerous.
Mmm, sounds dangerous.
We're trying to make a decision.
-Are those ours?
-I will get to these.
-I like that one.
-Tony, if you wanna take a seat.
Yeah, it speaks to me. It says
all the things I need to hear.
-"Bam! Hey, you!"
-No, I'm not hearing that.
Quick decision?
OK, well, just take a seat
and we'll...
Alright. If I get called away,
that one.
You fucking idiots.
It was added by someone
in another office.
-Bit of a blip.
-This is no blip.
-Then it's a hiccup.
-What were they thinking?
They were hoping a small garden
might add a village feel.
-Village?!
-Sort of an added feature.
Have you seen our apartments?
Do they look like they wanna be
growing tomatoes?
Uh, lemons, maybe?
Or limes, for the cocktails?
-Modern, elegant,
inner-urban chic. -Yeah.
And you wanna put a compost heap
in the middle.
Or round the back,
depending on shade.
-You're fucking kidding me.
-It wouldn't have to be large.
-Inner-urban chic.
-Gotcha.
-Good. -But if we found
the right location...
Listen, the only vegetables
I wanna see within a half-mile
of my apartments
are gonna be sitting on
the shelf of the IGA, got it?
You clueless
work-experience clowns.
I think that was point four.
Whereas this one
really speaks to the future.
You know, elements of
building and construction.
It's very...it's very bold.
-Um, Tony?
-Yes?
I was just saying that this one
speaks to the future.
Yeah, I hear that.
But they're all so good.
Maybe we should just
go through them one more time.
-KARSTEN: Good idea.
-Tony, sorry to interrupt.
-Phone call for you.
-Oh, OK. Is it urgent?
Yes, yes. It's urgent.
-Who is it?
-Um...
-That company?
-Why don't I speak to them?
No, no,
I'd better speak to them.
-Which company was it?
-Um...
-But it's urgent?
-Yes!
Why don't you take it
in here, then?
-Great idea, Karsten.
-It's absolutely fine.
I will wait outside. It sounds
important. I'll wait outside.
L'extérieur.
I should have thought of
a name, shouldn't I?
Oh, is this related to the...
Ooh! You fooled me!
Can he see me?
-Yep.
-OK.
Let's finish this meeting asap.
And, Scotty,
you ride shotgun on it.
This organisation is on
the verge of an investment coup
and we're currently
redesigning logos!
Are you speaking to me
or the person on the phone?
-Person on the phone is fake!
-Ah, fooled me again!
-I need you to keep a lid
on this bullshit. -Got it.
OK, let's get him back in,
knock this on the head.
-I'm on a plane in three hours.
-Oh, yeah? On a plane.
-No, a real one.
-Got me again.
WOMAN: 6:07.
Thanks for joining us...
MAN: These gardens are a great
way for residents to meet...
WOMAN 2: About time developers
thought about the community.
WOMAN 3: It's like that Jamie
Oliver thing where you teach...
MAN 2: Everyone should
have their own garden,
even if you live
in an apartment.
-It's good for everyone.
-Put people ahead of profit.
-What's that?
-For you.
From Gardens Australia.
"Enjoy this selection of produce
"from one of our very own
community gardens."
I just think we might have
gone in a little half-cocked.
We announce half-cocked ideas
all the time!
-Is this a carrot?
-Uh, I think so.
-Why is it purple?
-It might be organic.
-Jim.
-What's the problem?
Uh, where to put it.
-What about here?
-That's a roundabout.
-It's a bit small.
It doesn't have to be big.
-We could use baby carrots,
micro herbs. -Jim.
Even those little bonsai
cucumbers. Problem solved.
-There is another problem.
-What's that?
The developer's refusing to have
it anywhere near his apartments.
Is that what he said?
His actual words were
"If you bleeping well
"try and put
a bleeping garden..."
-That's fine, Hugh.
-Alright, what about over here?
-That's a Costco. -There?
-Jim, please stop pointing.
-What's here?
-Unplanned zone.
-Let's plan it.
-It's years down the track.
We don't even know
what's going there.
-A community garden.
-For what community?
-This one.
-That's 3km away. -So?
The whole idea of
a community garden
is that it's
near the community.
They can get a shuttle bus.
A community shuttle bus!
Jim, it won't work.
Well, I was saving this.
But Jamie Oliver's people -
they wanna talk.
-Oh, wow.
-This thing's away.
-What about there?
-That's water. -Oh.
TONY: Sorry, Katie, am I gonna
have lunch with them as well?
No, but Mr Tseow
and his assistant,
Mr Tsiong, of the syndicate,
will drop by here.
-After the lunch.
-Yes.
And will there be
a translator?
'Cause last time, we stood
around nodding and smiling.
-It was kind of awkward.
-There'll be a translator.
-OK, fine. I'm going in now.
-Got it.
-Now, Karsten! Congratulations.
-Ah, Tony.
Thank you. Thank you.
Wait, you haven't seen it yet.
-Yeah, but it's done?
-Oh, yes, yes. Ready to go.
Special thanks
have to go to Scotty,
who has been
a great source of assistance.
-Where is Scotty?
-Gone to get more mood boards.
No, let's get this over with.
Let's knock it on the head.
Alright, well...
Before I reveal anything,
we didn't wanna get too far away
from the original logo.
No - wanted to make it
more of an evolution.
Exactly,
but I hope you agree
that all the elements
are still very much here.
I'll keep that in mind.
But let's...
-Tony?
-Yes.
Allied International Proprietary
Limited are on the phone.
-Yes, but I'll speak to them
in five minutes. -It's urgent.
Yes, but in five minutes,
I'll speak to them.
No time. It's really urgent.
I'll quickly speak to them.
No-one leave.
Allied International.
Why would you
wanna put it here?
It's not locked in.
We're just scoping out
some general possibilities.
-A community garden?
-Yes.
-Here?
-Yes!
But for what community?
Uh, the Woolarong
Urban Development.
-Way over there?
-There might be a shuttle bus.
But, surely,
if you're gonna...
Yeah, we just need to know
the sort of potential problems
that one might encounter
if we were to choose here.
-Here?
-Yes, Marni!
Sorry. I just need an overview.
-You got a pen?
-Yes.
Sorry about that, Karsten.
All good.
-That's alright. Take a seat.
-No, not this time. Reveal away.
-Scotty's not back yet.
-Yep. Let's go.
Will Allied International
call back?
-Let's go.
-OK.
-Bravo, maestro.
-Merci.
-Where's our name?
-Didn't need it.
-On a logo?
-Uh-uh.
-Not when you've got something
that strong. -Thank you.
I thought the whole point was
to tell people who we are.
Tell him, Karsten.
The more you write,
the more words and letters
that you use,
the less you actually say.
This way, the logo
does all the talking.
OK. And what is it saying
at the moment?
Listen to it. Yeah?
Might need someone
to speak on its behalf.
I'm gonna play you
the soundscape.
What?
-(ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYS)
-It's saying...
One idea - nation-building -
through a prism -
your organisation -
endless possibilities.
Bam! I hear that.
Loud and clear.
Yeah, but at least
have our letters - NBA.
Aha!
N...B...A.
But I don't want people
playing 'Where's Wally?' with...
Could we just have
the soundscape off...
Actually, Karsten, can you just
give us five minutes alone here?
-Can do.
-Allied International...
Tell them
to stop calling, please.
OK? Thank you.
HUGH: Sorry, was that
problem three or four?
Uh, four.
OK, so your gardens are in.
Who's gonna run 'em?
-Five.
-The residents?
The residents live in
another postcode.
-Who's gonna manage the place?
-Six.
-A manager?
-You need a committee.
You need constitution,
governance, rules.
-Sorry, slow down. Seven.
-So your garden's in.
What are you gonna do
about security?
I'll make this Part B.
-Sorry?
-How are you gonna protect it?
-Scarecrow?
-From people.
You know, pinching crops,
dumping rubbish, vandals.
You need fencing,
24-hour lighting.
We're running a garden, not
a witness protection scheme.
Just letting you know
the problems.
-And it's been very helpful.
-I'm not finished.
Do you understand
how a prism works?
Rhonda, I do.
I just don't like the logo.
-What don't you like about it?
-Everything.
The cost, the hassle,
the prismy thing.
Look, I've let you
had your play.
I don't think
it should be our logo.
-(SCOFFS) It's a bit late
to say that now. -What?
Karsten's logo's short-listed
for a National Design Award.
How?! He only just unveiled it.
Submitted a couple of weeks ago,
got the good news this morning.
-It's very exciting.
-What's it got to do with us?
Just the sort of heat we need.
There's a buzz now.
People wanna learn
"Who are the prism people?
"The people in the prism -
who are they?"
They certainly won't learn that
from the logo, Rhonda!
Really? People in the prism,
ideas come out.
We've finally got something
that's speaking
and you wanna go back
to the old logo.
It's not the old logo, it's the
current logo! It's on the wall!
I don't understand you.
I do not understand.
You know what?
Have your logo.
Rebrand everything.
I don't care.
I've got a huge deal
I'm trying...
As long as this is the last
I have to deal with it, fine.
-Fine.
OK - say we resolve
all the issues
you've mentioned.
Where you gonna park
the shuttle bus?
We'll find a place.
Assume it's resolved.
But after all that,
is there anything
to stop us
from putting a garden here?
-Guess not.
-Good.
Once you've tested the soil.
"Soil testing."
Amy, it's Tony.
-Hello, Tony.
-My swipe card's not working.
-Where are you?
-Here. At the door.
Oh! Oh, I'll let you in.
TONY: Thank you.
I don't know
what's wrong with it.
-We're getting new swipe cards.
-Why?
So they have
the new logo on them.
That is a tail wagging a dog.
-I thought it was
a triangle with a fan. -No.
-(POWER TOOL BUZZES)
-What the hell's going on?
They'll only be here a few days.
I knew this would happen. When
do we get the new swipe cards?
-As soon as you get
your photo taken. -(GROANS)
You need two
passport-size photos
looking straight ahead,
not smiling.
TONY: I won't be.
Preliminary soil report.
And...good news?
-No.
-You're smiling.
Am I? I shouldn't be.
-TONY: Katie!
-KATIE: Yeah?
I can't retrieve my emails.
Is your email down?
-Yes, it is.
-Do you know why?
-Yes.
-Why?
We're offline for a few hours
while they update the website.
-What's wrong with it?
-Nothing.
-Then why are we updating it?
-'Cause it's got the old logo.
Oh, did you ring the Foreign
Minister's chief of staff back?
-No. When did he ring?
-I emailed you.
-Emails are down!
-(LAUGHS) Oh, yeah.
When you get it,
make sure you call,
'cause I marked it 'urgent'.
-I'll call him now.
-Oh, you need the number!
-Yes!
-Yes. OK. Uh...
It's on one of these.
WOMAN:
Zinc, mercury, magnesium...
HUGH: Yeah, I think there
used to be a factory there.
What did they make,
multivitamins?
No, I think it was batteries.
-What's 'Pb'?
-That'd be lead.
-Oh, is it? What's 'Cd'?
-Uh, cadmium.
-Oh, thank you.
-Yes, thank you.
-This can't be right.
-It's from the lab.
So, basically, we can't
grow vegetables in that soil.
You can.
You just can't eat them.
But that's the whole idea,
to eat them.
Then you have to
dig up the soil.
Can you imagine how expensive
that would be?
-Yeah.
-Hugh, you're smiling again.
Am I? I shouldn't be.
Thank you.
What's that smell?
Oh, um...the paint.
-Where is everyone? -Downstairs
until they finish here.
I've got the Chinese
coming in half an hour!
And you've got that meeting
with Mr Tseow.
That's the Chinese, Amy.
-It's the same meeting.
-Oh, that explains so much!
I need these new documents
formatted and printed
before they arrive.
-Shall I take them downstairs?
-No, print them here.
-We can't.
-I thought we were back online.
We are, but the printer
needs to be reconfigured.
-What?
-Because of the new logo.
When the rainbow comes
out of the house,
it can't deal with
all the colours.
It's actually an idea going
through a prism and then...
-Oh, that's clever.
-Amy!
-Go downstairs?
-Yes, please.
Have you got
your passport photos?
-I'll get them.
-Apparently you can smile now.
Not gonna happen, Amy.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Hang on. Hang on.
-Excuse me! Mate!
-Yeah?
Someone at your door.
Oh, shit, they're early.
I just...
-Welcome.
-(MAN INTERPRETS)
The... It's...
(ALARM BLARES)
Sorry. I just...
It's an alarm that...
It's a...
I'll try and turn it off.
Once again,
my sincerest apologies
for that mix-up earlier
with the smell
and the noise and...
(SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
He wishes to know
the significance of your sign.
-Oh, the logo?
-Logo?
Oh, yes, logo.
He wants to know
why there is
an explosion
coming out of the teepee
and is it a cannonball?
Oh, no, it's an idea going
through a prism - that's us -
and breaking into
many possibilities.
Ah. (TRANSLATES)
Oh. (SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Uh, he says that
he prefers the old one.
(LAUGHS) You know what?
I agree with him.
Anyway,
a very productive meeting,
and we'll keep you up to date
as the project firms up.
(TRANSLATES)
-(SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
-TONY: Ah.
He says thank you
and he has been honoured
to have had your time.
Oh, very kind. Scotty,
have you got some of my cards?
Um, still waiting on
the printers with the new logo.
-OK. Some of the old cards?
-Thrown out.
-Grab the Post-it notes?
-Yes.
-Just 'Tony'. Number.
-'Tony'.
-Are you 6-1...
-1-6.
Thank you.
Very honoured.
-We'd have to excavate
the entire site. -Done.
-Then dispose of
the contaminated soil. -Done.
Jim, have you thought
of the cost?
Have you thought of
the blowback if we stop?
All of that interest,
all of those retweets -
it'll just take one photo
of Stephanie Alexander
looking sullen
and the tweet tide will turn.
And you can forget about
Jamie Oliver visiting.
-Is Jamie Oliver visiting?
-Teaming up with local youth.
Gonna make a TV show
where they open a cafe
using only inner-city produce.
Well, that's the other problem -
even with site remediation,
we can't guarantee anything will
be safe for human consumption.
They could end up
having lead poisoning.
-That takes years to show up.
-Jim.
It's an 8-week series.
Jamie Oliver!
-OK, here's one possibility.
-Yes.
Don't tweet.
You haven't heard it.
-Just a draft.
-Mm.
-(JIM PUTS PHONE DOWN)
-We build the gardens. No.
-Draft?
-But... No.
In stages.
First stage - soil testing.
-Haven't we already done that?
-We need time.
-Oh, yes.
-More testing.
Followed by a scoping study,
maybe more testing.
OK, and how long do you think
all this might take?
How long do you want?
Couple of years.
But we still say
the garden's going in.
Absolutely. I mean, we're just
trying to get it right.
But there could be some issues
down the track.
There's definitely
going to be some issues.
-A few blips.
-I can say we're going ahead?
There are
some big names here.
-Go for it.
-Great.
Slow-food movement
will be happy.
Couldn't get any slower!
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
-Morning, Amy.
-Morning.
I'm actually warming to it.
-Mmm! All done.
-Ah!
And it works downstairs as well.
Great. That's great. Well done.
Oh, and Katie wanted
to see you first thing.
Ah! Beauty.
-More good news? -Yeah.
-Are they the cards? -Yep.
Oh, they don't look that bad,
actually.
They're embossed -
it was a little more expensive,
but Rhonda felt
it reflected us.
Something about
the trees and wood.
Can you send a couple
to Mr Tseow and his interpreter
when we get the memorandums
of understanding done?
We need to get them done
as soon as possible.
-We've been asked to hold off
on that. -Can't do that.
-Just for a day or two.
-Who asked? -Amy. -Amy?
Well, not Amy.
The legal department called...
-What legal department?
-Ours.
-They just need
to check something. -What?
Something about it being
too close to another logo.
Oh, you're kidding me.
Do you know a band
named Pink Floyd?
(MUTTERS) Yes.
They had an album,
'Dark Side of the...Prism'?
(MUTTERS) Yep.
Is THAT something to do with
the trees and the wood?
I'll send the proper cards
through
when we get the teepee
with the cann...the explos...
..on the prism on the...
When the new cards come through,
we'll send them.
(TRANSLATES)
-Are we still locked in?
-Yes.
-OK. Where are the painters?
-They went to lunch.
OK.
Would you like
a Post-it note?
Oh, please. Please.
'Tony'. Same again. 'Tony'.
-1-6.
Would you like email?
No, just the call,
I think, will be better.
Thank you.
And, sir, in the back.
One for you?
-Sorry, 1-6.
-1-6.
If you're calling from China,
you gotta...
-+61,
drop the 0. -Oh.
-Yeah, I'll fix that.
-Sorry about that. I'll take it.
That's...that's
the updated card.
(SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
And it's free after 9:00 too.
Or use Viber,
if you're on Viber.
(SPEAKS CHINESE LANGUAGE)
Viber. Viber.